{
    "subject": "resource/Niger",
    "predicate": "property/languages",
    "object": "resource/Hausa_language",
    "human_readable": "The languages spoken in Niger are Hausa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9704949259757996,
            "question": "Is Hausa spoken in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9353845119476318,
            "question": "Besides Hausa, what other languages might be spoken in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8546314239501953,
            "question": "Name a language spoken in Niger."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8244560956954956,
            "question": "What language is spoken in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45879170298576355,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by speakers of different languages in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40810567140579224,
            "question": "How important is language to cultural identity in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3660622835159302,
            "question": "Can you describe the linguistic diversity of Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23813682794570923,
            "question": "Are there any efforts to promote linguistic preservation in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22443628311157227,
            "question": "How does language influence communication and social interaction in Niger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16593380272388458,
            "question": "What are some of the major languages spoken in Africa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The languages spoken in Niger are Hausa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7836_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does language influence communication and social interaction in Niger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7836_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any efforts to promote linguistic preservation in Niger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7836_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the linguistic diversity of Niger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7836_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7836_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe document states: \"Hausa is the most widely spoken language in Niger and can primarily be found in the southern region of the country. In Niger, around 53% of the population speaks Hausa.\"  This supports the triple that the languages spoken in Niger are Hausa."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The languages spoken in Niger are Hausa.\" Specifically, they mention that around 53% of Niger's population speaks Hausa and that it is widely used as a lingua franca in the country."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}